Finding Aid for the USA for Africa Records LSC.1669
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mali / Niger / Senegal, 1985-1990
  - E.E.R.N. (Box 55, Folder 26-28)
    - Correspondence - 07008 [empty]. (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Project summary - 07008. (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Financial information - 07008. (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - I.S.A.I.D. (Box 55, Folder 29-32)
    - Correspondence - 07009. (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Project summary - 07009. (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Financial information - 07009. (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Progress report - 07009. (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - M.S.F. (Box 55, Folder 33-36)
    - Correspondence - 07010. (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Project summary - 07010. (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - Financial information - 07010. (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Progress reports - 07010. (Box 55, Folder 36)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mauritania, 1985-1990
  - Terre des Hommes - Progress report - 05402. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) (Box 71, Folder 2-5)
    - Correspondence - 05403. (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Progress report - 05403. (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Financial information - 05403. (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - 05403. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Unione Internazionale Handicappati Fisici e Mentali (UNHPM) (Box 71, Folder 6-10)
    - Project summary - 05404. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - 05404. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Progress report - 05404. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Financial information - 05404. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Unfoldered material. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - National Orthopaedic and Functional Rehabilitation Centre (CNORF) (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
    - Correspondence - 05405. (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Financial information - 05404. (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mauritania / Mozambique, 1985-1990
  - National Orthopaedic and Functional Rehabilitation Centre (CNORF) (Box 71, Box 72)
    - Project summary - 05405. (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Progress report - 05405. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - World Vision (Box 72, Folder 2-5)
    - Correspondence - 05406. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Project summary - 05406. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Financial information - 05406. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Progress report - 05406. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Non-governmental organizations/Community/Associations - Mauritania. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI) (Box 72, Folder 7-14)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.05901. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.05901. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Progress report - W.I.D. no.05901 [empty]. (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.05901. (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.05902. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.05902. (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Progress report - W.I.D. no.05902 [empty]. (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.05902. (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Save the Children Fund (SCF) (Box 72, Folder 15-19)
    - Correspondence - 06301. (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 06301. (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Budget - 06301. (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Procurement - 06301. (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Early proposal, negotiations, etc., before project site moved - 06301. (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mozambique, 1985-1990
  - Save the Children Fund (SCF) - Reports - 06301. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) (Box 73, Folder 2-3)
    - Correspondence - 06201. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 06201. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Payment schedule - 06203 [half of blue folder]., 1987-1988 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Operation Handicap International (Box 73, Folder 5-9)
    - Correspondence - 06203. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Budget - 06203. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 06203. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Reports - 06203. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Procurement - 06203. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Mozambique (Box 73, Box 74)
    - Progress report - 06105. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - General. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Medical airlift. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - R&RR - United Nations Development Programme - 06102. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - R&RR - United Nations Development Programme - 06103. (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - R&RR - United Nations Development Programme - 06104. (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - R&RR - U.N.I.C.E.F. - 06105. (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - R&RR - U.D.A.A.S. (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - American Red Cross. (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - R&RR - Report - ARC. (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - M.O.H. - 06302 (Box 73, Box 74)
      - [No further description available]. (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence - 06302. (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Proposal & Grant Application - 06302. (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Budget - 06302. (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Request for additional funds - 06302. (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Procurement - 06302. (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Report - 06302. (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Unfoldered material - Malaria control. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - AirServ (Box 74, Folder 7-9)
    - Financial information - no.06509. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Project summary - no.06509. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - no.06509. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Mozambique Health Commission (Box 74, Folder 10-15)
    - Reports - 06405. (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Procurement/not used - 06405. (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Procurement used - 06405. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 06405. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 06405. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - 06405. (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - N.C.N.W. (Box 75, Folder 1-7)
    - Correspondence no.1 - 06406. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence no.2 - 06406. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 06406. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Progress report - 06406. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Supplemental report no.1 - 06406. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Supplemental report no.2 - 06406. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Project summary - 06406. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - N.I.P.P. (Box 75, Folder 8-11)
    - Correspondence - 06407. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Progress report - 06407. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - 06407. (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Financial - 06407. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Oxfam/U.S. (Box 75, Box 76)
    - Progress reports - 06408 [empty]. (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 06408. (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 06408. (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Procurement - 06408. (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - 06408. (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Project summary - 06409. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Progress report - 06409. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 06409. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - 06409. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Mozambique Health Commission (Box 76, Folder 5-10)
    - Project summary - 06411. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Progress reports - 06411. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Procurement - 06411. (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - 06411. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Procurement (unused) - 06411. (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - 06411. (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Technica (Box 76, Folder 11-13)
    - Project summary - no.06704. (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Progress reports - no.06704. (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - no.06704. (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) - Irrigation - 06008. (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Mozambique Health Assessment Mission (contribution). (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - A.R.O. (Box 77, Folder 1-3)
    - Financial information - 06001. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - 06001. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Project summary - 06001. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Biforce (Box 77, Folder 4-6)
    - Correspondence - 06002. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - 06002. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Financial information - 06002. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Mozambique Health Commission - Third report - 06411 [black binder]. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Community Aid Abroad (Box 77, Folder 8-11)
    - Project reports - 06003. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - 06003. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - 06003. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Project information - 06003. (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - People to People (Box 77, Folder 12-15)
    - Correspondence - 06004. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 06004. (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Progress reports. (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Project summary - 06004. (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Eduardo Mondlane Foundation (Box 77, Box 78)
    - Correspondence - 06005. (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Project reports - 06005. (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Project summary - 06005. (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Financial information - 06005. (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Unfoldered material. (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - 06006. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Project reports - 06006 [empty]. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Biforce (Box 78, Folder 5-7)
    - Correspondence - 06007. (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Project summary - 06007. (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - 06007. (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) - Irrigation - 06008. (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Mozambique (Box 78, Box 79)
    - General information. (Box 78, Folder 9-12, 18)
    - Unfoldered material - General information. (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Contact lists. (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Country background. (Box 78, Folder 15-16)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Non-governmental organizations/Community/Associations. (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Coweslo Cristo (Box 79, Folder 2, 6)
    - Project summary - 06403. (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - 06403. (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - C.C.M. (Box 79, Folder 3-5)
    - Progress reports - 06403 [empty]. (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Financial - 06403. (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - GA's-- hold for response - 06403. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Mozambique Anglican Church (Box 79, Folder 7-10)
    - Financial - 06410. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Progress report - 06410 [empty]. (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - 06410. (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - 06410. (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - A.F.S.C. (Box 79, Folder 11-15)
    - Supplemental material - 06401. (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Progress report - 06401. (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - 06401. (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 06401. (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - 06401. (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Mozambique Red Cross (Box 79, Folder 16-19)
    - Correspondence - no.06R02. (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Progress reports - no.06R02 [empty]. (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - no.06R02. (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Project summary - no.06R02. (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - AirServ 1-2. (Box 79, Folder 20-21)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Niger / Senegal, 1985-1990
  - World Food Programme (WFP) (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence - 07011. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 07011. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 07011. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Africare (Box 56, Folder 4-7)
    - Correspondence - 07012. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Progress report - 07012. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Project summary - 07012. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - 07012. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Tango organizations (Box 56, Folder 8-11)
    - Project summary - no.08408. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - no.08408. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Background information, etc. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - no.08408. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI)/A.N.I.D. (Box 56, Folder 12-15)
    - Correspondence - 08401. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Project summary - 08401. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Progress report - 08401. (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - 08401. (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Association JdeR (Box 56, Folder 16-20)
    - Correspondence - 08402. (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Project summary - 08402. (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Unfoldered material - "Proformas UGM 08402" [manila envelope]. (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Financial information - 08402. (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - U.G.M. - Progress report - 08402. (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI)/A.J.A.C. (Box 56, Folder 21-24)
    - Correspondence - 08403. (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Project summary - 08403. (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Progress report - 08403. (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 08403. (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Fed. du Balantacounda (Box 56, Folder 25-27)
    - Correspondence - 08404. (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Project summary - 08404. (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Financial information - 08404. (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - N.C.N.W. (Box 56, Folder 28-31)
    - Correspondence - 08405. (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Financial information - 08405. (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Project summary - 08405. (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Progress report - 08405. (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Forum of African Voluntary Development Organization (FAVDO) (Box 57, Folder 1-5)
    - Proposal - BG 604. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Budget & meeting reports - BG 604. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Reports/new proposal. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Meeting minutes - BG 604. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Reports - BG 604. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Association for African Women on Research and Development (AAWORD) (Box 57, Folder 6-10)
    - Correspondence - BG 602. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - BG 602. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Summary information - BG 602. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Progress report - BG 602. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Unfoldered material - "Publications - Association for African Women on Research and Development (AAWORD) - BG 602" [manila envelope]. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI) (Box 57, Folder 11-13)
    - Correspondence - 08406. (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 08406. (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 08406. (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Union pour development (Box 57, Folder 14-16)
    - Correspondence - 08407. (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Project summary - 08407. (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Financial information - 08407. (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI)/U.B.D. - Progress report - 08407 [empty]. (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Femme Developpement Entreprise en Afrique (FDEA) (Box 57, Folder 18-21)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.08901. (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.08901. (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.08901. (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Progress report - 08901. (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Association Nationale des Handicapes Moteurs du Senegal (ANHMS) (Box 57, Folder 22-24)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.08902. (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.08902. (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.08902. (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - A.F.O.T.E.C. (Box 57, Box 58)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.08903. (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.08903. (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Project summary. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.08903. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Centre for Development and Population Activities (CEDPA) (Box 58, Folder 3-7)
    - Senegal [empty]. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.08904. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.08904. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.08904. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Unfoldered material - CEDPA 1989 Annual report - 08904. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - M.F.R. (Box 58, Folder 8-10)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.08905. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.08905. (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.08905. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Africare (Box 58, Folder 11-13)
    - Financial information - 08001. (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 08001. (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - 08001. (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - French Association of Volunteers of Progress - Financial information - 08002. (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - French Association of Volunteers of Progress (Box 58, Folder 15-16)
    - Correspondence - 08002. (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Project summary - 08002. (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - P.A.D.E.C. (Box 58, Folder 17-24)
    - Project summary - 08003. (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - 08003. (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Financial information - 08003. (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous reports - 08003. (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Progress reports - 08003. (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Project summary - 08004. (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - 08004. (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 08004. (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - E.E.L.S. (Box 58, Folder 25-31)
    - Project summary - 08005. (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - 08005. (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - Financial information - 08005. (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Financial information - 08006. (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Reports - 08006. (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence - 08006. (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Project summary - 08006. (Box 58, Folder 31)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Non-Target Countries, 1985-1990
  - Miscellaneous information. (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Chad - R&RR - General. (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous information - All Africa [empty]. (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Maps. (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Audio-visual resources. (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - R&RR - Contact list. (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 92, Folder 7, 9, 11)
  - R.R.H. - Non-governmental organizations address list. (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Lieberman Enterprises/University of Minnesota - Food resource development. (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Non-governmental organizations - International. (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Partnership Africa Canada. (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - R.A.F.A.D. (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Save the Children Foundation. (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Solidarite Canada Sahel. (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - S.O.S.-Sahel. (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Trickle Up. (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - United Nations non-governmental liaison service. (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - World education. (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - World Resources Institute. (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Africa - General information. (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Non-governmental organizations/Community/Associations - Other. (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Airlift (Box 93, Folder 8-18, 20-21, 23-29)
    - June 10, 1985. (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Americo International. (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Birkin Manufacturing. (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Coleman & Company. (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Ethiopian Airlines. (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Flying Tigers. (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Halsey Drug Company, Incorporated. (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Henderson Camp Products, Incorporated. (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Jianas Brothers Packaging. (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - P. Leiner Nutrition Products. (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Mark Clark Company. (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Metalized Products. (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Monsanto. (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Richylyn Laboratory, Incorporated. (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Ross Laboratories. (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Saber Freight Systems. (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - Henry Schein, Incorporated. (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Sherwood Medical. (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Starboard Group. (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Travenol Laboratories. (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Medical Chemicals Corporation. (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Operation California. (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - C.I.F.A.D. (Box 93, Folder 30-33)
    - Financial information - no.14901. (Box 93, Folder 30)
    - Project summary - no.14901. (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 93, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence - no.14901. (Box 93, Folder 33)
  - Djibouti - Non-governmental organizations/Community/Associations. (Box 93, Folder 34)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - U.U.S.C. - Benin. (Box 93, Folder 36)
  - Kenya (Box 94, Folder 1-5)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - HNA04. (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - HNA04. (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Progress report - HNA04. (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - HNA04. (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Tanzania (Box 94, Folder 6-7)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Newsclippings. (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Uganda. (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Country background - Other [empty]. (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - South Africa (Box 94, Folder 10-11)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Newsclippings. (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Southern Africa - Newsclippings [empty]. (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - World Vision (Box 94, Folder 14-17)
    - Correspondence - no.12501. (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - no.12501. (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Progress report - no.12501. (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Project summary - no.12501. (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - CC New York/Solomon Mahlangu Freedom College (Box 94, Folder 18-21)
    - Correspondence - no.12101. (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Financial information - no.12101. (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Progress summary - no.12101. (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Progress report - no.12101. (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Ambulance - Moshi Village (Box 94, Folder 22-25)
    - [Empty]. (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - 11202. (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Proposals & grant application - 11202. (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - Budget - 11202. (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Immaculate Heart Sisters (Box 94, Folder 26-29)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.12901. (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.12901. (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.12901. (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - Other - no.12WD917. (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - University of Wisconsin (Box 95, Folder 1-5)
    - Payment schedule - 11302. (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - 11302. (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Proposals & grant application - 11302. (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Budget - 11302. (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Reports - 11302. (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Project Sida (Box 95, Folder 6-11)
    - Payment schedule - 11203. (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - 11203. (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Proposals & grant application - 11203. (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Budget - 11203. (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Zaire - Procurement - 11203. (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Reports - 11203. (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - A.A.P. (Box 95, Folder 12-15)
    - Correspondence - 11306. (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Proposals &GA - 11306. (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Reports - 11306. (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Budget - 11306. (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Synergos (Box 95, Folder 16-19)
    - Correspondence - BG 612. (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - BG 612. (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - BG 612. (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Narrative & financial report. (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Association of Women's Clubs (Box 95, Folder 20-23)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.17901. (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.17901. (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.17901. (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Other - no.99WD905. (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Zimbabwe (Box 95, Box 96)
    - Correspondence - HNA03-A. (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Project summary - HNA03-A. (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Financial information - HNA03-A. (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - HNA03-A. (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Project summary - HNA03-B. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Financial information - HNA03-B. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Old proposals. (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Somalia (Box 96, Folder 4-10)
    - R&RR - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees - 08101. (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - R&RR - W Concern - 08012. (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - R&RR - Report - WC. (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - HNA02. (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Financial information - HNA02. (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Project summary - HNA02. (Box 96, Folder 9-10)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 96, Folder 11)